原文：subhd
电影Robin And The 7 Hoods 字幕
People dress 'cause they like to get dressed
人们穿衣服是因为他们喜欢穿衣服
翻译，特效，压制：布尔
But you just dress to get dressed
但是你只是为了穿而穿
It's only a hunch but I bet you a bunch
我敢在这不靠谱的预感上打包票
样式范例：Others Bing Crosby
Frank Sinatra Dean Martin
He wears suspenders, a belt and a vest
他穿着吊带裤 腰带 还有马甲
样式范例：Frank Sinatra & Dean Martin
Bing Crosby & Frank Sinatra & Dean Martin
Am I correct in my assumption that
我的假設沒錯吧
you gentleman find my habiliments reprehensible?
我推斷你們這些紳士覺得我的衤箙有傷風化
字体：思源宋体 SemiBold
配色：Solarized
Think some wrong with his throat.
我感觉是他的嗓子出了问题
I told him six weeks ago.
我六周前就跟他说了
From the tip of your toes to your head
你浑身上下
You look like an unmade bed
都糟糕得像一床没铺的被子
Now I hate to belabor the obvious,
我不想過度研究顯而易見的事情
but in the interest of semantics,
但是從語義學這個角度着想
l'm impelled to observe you just indulged in a mixed metaphor.
我被你們驅使着研究你們沉溺其中的混雜隱喻
No, It's his throat. His throat.
不 这是因为他的嗓子
You've either got or you haven't got style
你到底有没有特点啊
If you got it, you stand out a mile
如果你有了自己的特点 那简直比现在显眼了不知多少
A flower's not a flower if it's wilted
枯萎的花儿要被开除出花籍
A hat's not a hat till it's tilted
歪着的帽子则要被开除出帽籍
You either got or you haven't got class
你够不够优雅啊
How it draws the applause of the masses
优雅的气质是如何吸引人们带来阵阵掌声的
When you wear lapels like the swellest of swells
当你的翻领穿得和那些最时髦的人一样
You can pass any mirror and smile
你就能在路过任何镜子时微笑
You either got, or you haven't got
你到底有没有
Got or you haven't got
Got or you haven't got style
你到底有没有特点啊
Nah, try this.
不行 快试试这个
You've either got or you haven't got style
你到底有没有特点啊
Got or you haven't got style
If you've got it, you stand out a mile
如果你有了自己的特点 那简直比现在显眼了不知多少
Got it, you stand out a mile
You look like something of a disaster area
看起来你糟透了
You think I'm too bizarre?
你觉得我太奇怪了吗
No, I think you're too carnival. Get out of here.
不 我觉得你太花里胡哨了 快离开这儿换一件
With mother of pearl kind of buttons
有珍珠母这类的纽扣
You'll look like the Astors and Huttons
你就会像Astor或者Hutton那些有钱人一样出色
You've either got or you haven't got class
你够不够优雅啊
Got or you haven't got class
How it draws the applause of the masses
优雅的气质是如何吸引人们带来阵阵掌声的
When you wear lapels like the swellest of swells
当你的翻领穿得和那些最时髦的人一样
You can pass any mirror and smile
你就能在路过任何镜子时微笑
Do you mind?
你们还介意吗
Well!
妙啊
You've either got or you haven't got charm
你到底有没有点魅力啊
Got or you haven't got charm
Style and charm sort of go arm in arm
特点和魅力可有点如影随形
They kind of go arm in arm
特点和魅力可有点相伴相生
A flower's not a flower if it's wilted
枯萎的花儿要被开除出花籍
A hat's not a hat till it's tilted
歪着的帽子则要被开除出帽籍
You've either got or you haven't got style
你到底有没有特点啊
Got or you haven't got style
If you got it, you stand out a mile
如果你有了自己的特点 那简直比现在显眼了不知多少
Got it, you stand out a mile
When you wear those duds
你穿着那些
Duds with black tie and studs
那些有黑领带的衣服时
Watch those dolls lining up single file
而浪子们看着那些美人站成一列
You've either got or you haven't got
你到底有没有
Got or you haven't got
你到底有没有特点啊
你到底有没有
Got or you haven't got
Style
自己的特点啊